(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-05T16:24:01.928144",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
最近行ったのよ、カラオケ。
I went to karaoke recently.
なんか2時間で解散と思うじゃん？そこからなのよ！
You'd think it breaks up after two hours. That's when it gets good!
いろんなことできるわけ。
There's so much you can do.
やばいぞ、すげえ！
It's awesome, seriously!
PLAY! NEW X. X PARK
X PARK最高！
X PARK is the best!
JOYSOUND X1
全国のアミューズメント施設にて宝鐘マリン限定プライズが順次展開中！
Houshou Marine limited prizes are rolling out at amusement facilities nationwide!
寝そべりぬいぐるみ
Neso-beri Plushie
パペットぬいぐるみ
Puppet Plushie
大判マウスパッド
Large Mouse Pad
ドクロくん トイレペーパーホルダー
Dokuro-kun Toilet Paper Holder
対象機に500円投入でオリジナルショッパーを1枚プレゼント！
Insert 500 yen into eligible machines to get one original shopper!
宝鐘マリン 1st Live
Houshou Marine 1st Live
ご来場のお客様へ
Attention to All Visitors
受注生産グッズ 1
Made-to-Order Goods 1
受注生産グッズ 2
Made-to-Order Goods 2
受注生産グッズ 3
Made-to-Order Goods 3
受注生産グッズ 4
Made-to-Order Goods 4
宝鐘マリン 危機一発
Houshou Marine Pop-Up Pirate
宝鐘マリン 1/7スケールフィギュア
Houshou Marine 1/7 Scale Figure
宝鐘マリン プロデュース香水
Houshou Marine Produced Perfume
マリンタワーコラボ
Marine Tower Collaboration
マリンです
I'm Marine!
本物のマリンです Ahoy!
The real Marine! Ahoy!
わあ！
Yay!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
さあ大事な話します
Now, I have an important announcement.
本日は宝鐘マリンファーストライブ Ahoy! 君たちみんなパイレーツ!にご来場いただきまして誠にありがとうございます
Thank you very much for attending Houshou Marine's 1st Live, "Ahoy! You're All Pirates!" today!
ありがとうございます
Thank you very much!
開演に先立ちまして お客さまにご注意並びにご案内申し上げます
Before the performance begins, we have a few notices and announcements for our guests.
公演中の撮影 録音 録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします
Photography, audio, and video recording equipment during the show are strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております
The venue is strictly non-smoking.
喫煙はご遠慮下さいますようお願い申し上げます
Please refrain from smoking.
万が一 体調に異変を感じる場合は 無理をせず係員へお申し付けください
In the unlikely event you feel unwell, please do not push yourself and notify a staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ ダイブ カタグルマ ステージ上に物を投げ込む
Mosh pits, stage diving, carrying people on shoulders, throwing objects onto the stage,
ステージ上に上がる 通路を塞ぐ 前に押し寄せる
climbing onto the stage, blocking aisles, rushing to the front,
周囲のお客様のご迷惑となるような不自然なコール 規制 公演の妨げとなる大きな音を鳴らすなどの行為
unnatural calls and chants that disturb surrounding guests, and acts that disrupt the performance like making loud noises,
不自然なタイミングで両手を左右に激しく振る 腕を振り回す 上半身を反らすなどの過激な応援行為
radically swinging arms, bending the upper body backwards, and other excessive cheering behaviors at unnatural timings,
他のお客様のご迷惑になる または公演を妨げる危険行為は一切禁止です
and other dangerous behaviors that inconvenience other guests or disrupt the performance are strictly prohibited.
本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り 客席のお客さまの様子が映り込む場合がございます
Please note that cameras for video streaming and photography will be inside the venue, and audience members' appearances may be captured.
これらの映像は これらの映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能性がございますのであらかじめご容赦ください
Please understand in advance that these footages and photos may be used for promotions and other purposes.
それではまもなく開演いたします お席についてお待ちください！
The performance will begin shortly. Please take your seats and wait!
おおー！
Ooh!
ドキドキしてルージュ？
Doki-doki, making you blush?
いきましょー！
Let's go!
（無罪！無罪！美少女無罪！）
(Not guilty! Not guilty! Innocent pretty girl!)
（マリン！マリン！マリンは無罪！）
(Marine! Marine! Marine is innocent!)
（やっぱりキラキラもっとクラクラ）
(Sparkling even brighter, getting even more dizzy)
ねえ、言ったよね？年齢なんて関係ないってさ
Hey, you said it, right? Age doesn't matter at all
そういうめんどくさいも含めて愛してくれるって
And that you'd love me even with all my troublesome traits
ねえねえ、言ったよね？言ってない？不運、そういうこと言うんだ
Hey hey, you said it, right? Or did you not? Hmm, so that's how it is.
ちなみにこの船では美少女無罪が適用されますけど？
By the way, the "Innocent Pretty Girl" rule applies on this ship, you know?
まかせて！魔法で若返り
Leave it to me! Rejuvenated by magic
ヒミツの素顔はキミにだけ
My secret true face is just for you
【トクベツです～？】
[It's special, okay~?]
ah… アタクシ厄介よ
Ah... I'm a handful, you know
ah… 港なんかじゃはしゃげないわ最近はね 宝の島にしてほしい気分
Ah... Lately I can't get excited just around ports, I'm in the mood to make it an island of treasure!
（出航ーー！！）
(Set sail--!!)
キュートは正義　美少女無罪
Cute is justice, innocent pretty girl
キミの一番目指してヨーソロー！
Aiming to be your number one, yosoro~!
本当は自信ないけど頑張っちゃうし
To be honest I'm not confident, but I'll do my best
（ahoy！！）
(ahoy!!)
きゅっ　きゅっ　きゅるん　きゅっ　きゅっ　きゅるんるん
Kyu kyu kyurun, kyu kyu kyurun run
恋する気持ち17歳　テッペンになっちゃうわ　大人の時間
A heart in love at 17 years old, it's hitting midnight, adult time
（やっぱりキラキラもっとクラクラ）
(Sparkling even brighter, getting even more dizzy)
ドキドキしてルージュ？　まだ早い♡
Doki-doki, making you blush? Still too early♡
だだだダメですか？　フリル 服着たら
Ba-ba-bad, is it? When I wear ruffled clothes
【そんなこと、ないよ】
[No way, that's not true]
だだだだって　魔法少女になってみたい
Ba-ba-but, I want to try becoming a magical girl
【ギリギリ有罪！？】
[Barely guilty!?]
真実は何なんだせい、ちょっぴり足りない積極性？
The truth is whatever, a little lacking in proactiveness?
（結局キミももっと若い子？）
(In the end you also prefer younger girls?)
【何だかすから見捨てないで、キミたち！】
[I'll do anything, so don't abandon us, you guys!]
（ちょっといいとこ見せてみた～い！）
(I wanna see your cool side a bit~)
ah… たまにいじけちゃう
Ah... Sometimes I get sulky
ah… それでもいいの？年頃もあって本気にしてしまう
Ah... Is that still okay? I'm at that age, so I'll take it seriously
嵐の中も
Even in the middle of a storm
【一緒に、行こう？】
[Shall we go together?]
（出航ーー！！）
(Set sail--!!)
ハートにチャーム　美少女無罪
Charm on your heart, innocent pretty girl
あれあれどうした？めんどくさいななんて言っちゃってさ
Well, well, what's wrong? Saying things like "it's such a hassle"
かまってくれるキミが好き
I love you who still pay attention to me
（ahoy！！）
(ahoy!!)
きゅっ　きゅっ　きゅるん　きゅっ　きゅっ　きゅるんるん
Kyu kyu kyurun, kyu kyu kyurun run
優しくしてね17歳
Treat me gently, 17 years old
突っ込んで経験値お楽しみchu♡
Dive in and enjoy the experience chu♡
（やっぱりキラキラもっとクラクラ）
(Sparkling even brighter, getting even more dizzy)
ドキドキしてルージュ？
Doki-doki, making you blush?
【あっ、お許しくだた～い！このマリンの…】
[Ah, please forgive me! This Marine's...]
（魅力！魔力！不抗力！）
(Charm! Magic! Irresistible force!)
――“罪な女”ね？
You're a "sinful woman", huh?
離さないでつかまっていて
Don't let go, hold on tight
世界の広さ見せてげられるから！
I'll show you how vast the world is!
（出航ーー！！）
(Set sail--!!)
キュートは正義　美少女無罪
Cute is justice, innocent pretty girl
キミの一番目指してヨーソロー！
Aiming to be your number one, yosoro~!
冗談も大好きだけど真剣よ
I love joking around, but I'm serious
（ahoy！！）
(ahoy!!)
きゅっ　きゅっ　きゅるん　きゅっ　きゅっ　きゅるんるん
Kyu kyu kyurun, kyu kyu kyurun run
恋する気持ち17歳
A heart in love at 17 years old
テッペンになっちゃうわ　大人の時間
It's hitting midnight, adult time
（やっぱりキラキラもっとクラクラ）
(Sparkling even brighter, getting even more dizzy)
ドキドキしてルージュ？　まだ早い♡
Doki-doki, making you blush? Still too early♡
（無罪！無罪！美少女無罪！）
(Not guilty! Not guilty! Innocent pretty girl!)
（マリン！マリン！マリンは無罪！）
(Marine! Marine! Marine is innocent!)
（やっぱりキラキラもっとクラクラ）
(Sparkling even brighter, getting even more dizzy)
【“マリン”じゃなくて、“マリン船長”だろーん！？】
[It's not "Marine", it's "Captain Marine"?!]
私どもの そう私どもの 千の黄金
My very own, yes, my very own, a thousand pieces of gold.
数百年の財宝 この船に眠る
Centuries of treasure sleep within this ship.
古びた伝説は 呪われた幽霊船に
An ancient legend leads to a cursed ghost ship.
続く夜の潮路 そこに富が残る
The continuous night tide, where wealth remains.
海賊の夢があるなら 頂くしかないでしょ？
If you have a pirate's dream, you must reach the top, right?
「無謀な赤よ 若き盗人よ」
"Foolish red ones, young thieves,"
「命をもってた 後悔に代えさせてやろう」
"Bring your lives and pay with regret."
止まない雨の弾丸で
With unceasing rain and bullets,
(駆け込む鼓動 まだこの足走れるはず)
(Beating heart, these feet can still run.)
美しいほど この瞳焦がす 生命の炎
So breathtakingly, this pupil burns with the flame of life.
(ガーネットの色彩 貴方にはない)
(Garnet colors, you don't possess.)
ガーネットの色彩 掴む 宝石なんなら
If you're clawing at garnet colors and precious stones,
私どもの そう私どもの 奪ってみろ
My very own, yes, my very own, try to take them.
命の証を 貴方の求める全てを
Proof of life, everything you desire.
輝きはくすんで 錆びつくだけて
Fading and rusting away,
それでも 泥舟にしがみつくなら 泡沫と共に沈め
Even so, if you cling to a sinking boat, sink with the foam.
黒い帆に 隠れる “極上の海賊の秘宝” 掴んで笑う
Hidden by the black sails, "The ultimate pirate's treasure," grabbed with a smile.
満月の金銀珠玉 七つの海の宝玉に
Gold and silver, jewels of the full moon, seven sea treasures.
「集る虫ども」 こぞり富を狙う 愚か者に思い知らす
"Gathering insects," making fools who covet wealth realize
相応しい持ち主を
They found a master worthy of them.
船に宿る黒い魂の群れ
Black souls residing in the ship,
影の底で忍び寄る絶望の渦
A desperate vortex creeping in the shadows,
まるで蓋の閉じた箱
Just like a box with the lid closed.
(光が消えれば 誰もお前を忘れ去るだけ)
(When the light fades, everyone forgets you.)
手放しちゃえば 諦めちゃえば
If you let go, if you give up,
悪夢の中から逃げられるのに まだ掴んでいる
You could escape from the nightmare, yet you still cling to it.
欲望が重いから (逃げられるのに まだ枷負って嘆息呼ぶ？)
Because your desires are heavy, (Even though you can escape, you still sigh with a heavy burden?)
自分自身を信じ込ませて 縛って 縛り付けてって 気付いた
Believing in yourself, bound and tethered, you finally realized.
呪いの出口 永久の夜の海域 目を覚まして 貴方の悪夢から
The exit of the curse, the sea of eternal night, wake up from your nightmare.
連れ出す幽霊船よ 出航して
Ghost ship leading the way, set sail and...
私どもの まだ私どもの 純紅のバラ 朽ち果てたとしても
My very own, still my very own, pure red rose, even if it withers away,
枯れない魂までは 万の幽霊 永遠的美貌
Until the undying soul, a myriad of spirits, eternal beauty.
そんな幻どうこうでいいでしょう 手放す決意はついたかい
Such an illusion is fine, isn't it? Have you made up your mind to let go?
さあ行こう 夜明けに舵を向けて
Now let's go, turning the rudder toward the dawn,
暁を宿した船 希望だけ 残して航く 他にはもういらないから
Sailing with only hope, we need nothing more.
Ah-hoy DADA-DA-AH
幽霊の先を
Deep in the shadows.
優しくそして Ah-hoy DADA-DA-AH
Treating gently, Ah-hoy, DADA-DA-AH.
宝庫の扉
Treasure door.
マジで早く開けて
Open it up quickly.
Ah-hoy DADA-DA-AH
絡れえたいあなたの手 纏い付く甘い溜息の気泡
Entangled in your hands, the lingering breath of a sweet stew.
たった一輪のバラが 散レル前に
Before a single rose is shattered,
聞きなさいよ
Listen, let me tell you.
七つの大海を 「Sまりwith glee」
The seven oceans contest, "Sまり with glee",
再び 輝き進め シャドウもシャドワリ
Cascading once again, shining shadows.
また手荒だから 何処覗いてんの
Again, where are you looking, wandering the seas?
The crisp round boundary is key
Open artist's pose Openいだいな
Open up, artist's pose, open wider!
Oh I wish I be alone
Oh, I wish I could be there alone.
Ah...
開けろ！
Open up!
寝盗も出歩る 名残のさよなら お前達ももう黙っていられなくなる
The lingering parting of the last night, you too can no longer remain.
you're gonna get the treasure
maybe tasting me
私の全てを 手に入れて
Take all of me into your hands,
ざわめく夜の蝶
you restless butterfly of the night.
Ah-hoy!
金銀財宝はした金でしょ
Gold and silver treasure is just pocket change!
しわしわになっちゃう
I'll end up all wrinkled up!
誰か助けて マジで遠征しすぎ
Someone help me, seriously, you're exploring too much!
キミたち何考えてんの？
What on earth are you guys thinking?
馬鹿って濡らすのはカストル
You fools getting me all wet...
だから今すぐ暴れさせてよ
So let me run wild right now!
さあ、だからば
So come on, then...
あなたを待つがねぇと
If I'm kept waiting for you,
さあ、キミたち上げて
come on, raise your hands up, everyone!
私のもの そう、私のもの
Mine, yes, entirely mine—
千年の数百年のお宝 この船に眠る
the treasure of centuries sleeps on this ship.
揺るぎだ伝説は 呪われたユーレイ船に
The unshakable legend tells of a cursed ghost ship,
朽ち夜の長老
decaying into the night's elder.
そこに神が残る 飼い慣れない目が有るのなら
If there's a stubborn god left behind there, with untamable eyes,
誓ったはずじゃないでしょ
didn't you promise otherwise?
無謀だよ若きヌストよ 命も持って怖がりに行かせてやろう
How reckless, young thief, risking your life to go feel the fear!
雨のしおだんだんで 恋しいほどこの瞳を濡らす
In the salty rain, these eyes are drenched with longing,
麗の炎 金糸の色彩からう
as the beautiful flame and golden threads intertwine.
私のもの そう、私のもの
Mine, yes, entirely mine—
命の証を
proof of life itself.
あなたの求める 全てを輝くわ
Shine upon everything you desire,
色褪せずいつまでも それでも踊れ
unfading, forevermore. Dance on anyway,
泥に錆びつくなら
if you're going to rust in the mud.
黒い瞳に映る 漆黒の海の地方
Reflected in those black eyes, the remote regions of a pitch-black sea,
飼い慣れない地方 帰れば笑う
untamable lands—if I return, I'll laugh.
満月の金銀修行 七つの海の波を
A full moon's gold and silver training, across the waves of seven seas,
宝の虫ども
aiming for the treasure's insects.
蝙蝠瞳を狙う
Targeting those bat-like eyes,
闇夜に思い知らす
making them realize the dark of night.
裁きを主を
Imposing judgment on the Lord.
船に宿る 黒い魂の群れ
Swarms of black souls dwelling in the ship,
影の底で忍び寄る 欲望の渦まるで
creeping in the depths of shadows like a vortex of desire.
鍵のかじった箱
A key-gnawed box—
手放しちゃえば 諦めちゃう
if you let go, if you give up,
闇の中から 逃げられるのに なぜか狂える
you could escape from the darkness, but why go crazy instead,
夜を求めから
asking for the night?
私のもの そう、私のもの
Mine, yes, entirely mine—
自分自身を 信じ込ませてしまって 縛りつけてだって
making yourself truly believe, tying yourself down,
気づいた
and then you realized.
運命の出口 永遠の夜の懐起
The exit of fate, the eternal embrace of the night,
目を覚まして あなたの箱から
wake up, and from your box,
連れ出す秘密だよ
it's a secret that leads you out!
余命数ヶ月ばかりの恋に
With only a few months left to love,
点滴で扶養する患者達
Patients sustained by IV drips,
被害者の甘い期待を弄び 悔悟の機会を蔑むドクター
Doctors who play with sweet hopes and scorn remorse,
所為など行方知らず
Whereabouts unknown,
未知の病巣に臥す患者達
Patients bedridden with an unknown disease,
発熱が死因 然らば早期に
Fever is the cause of death—if so,
蔑むべきだったと知る放火犯
We should have scorned it early on, the arsonist knows.
この体に穴が開いたくらいなのに
Even though my heart is pierced with a hole,
たったそれだけの違いなのに
Even though that should be the only difference,
貴方の背中に滲んでる涙痕が
Why do the blurred tear marks on your back
乾きそうもないのはどうしてなんだろ
Look like they're never going to dry?
病名は愛だった
The disease was love.
今はもはや持ち腐れの恋に
Now, in this rusted love,
些事な延命を乞う患者達
Patients begging for petty life support,
加害者の荒い治療に耐えたい
Enduring the rough treatment of the culprit,
伴侶たる者と覚えるペイシェント
Patients feeling like true companions.
赤い糸を固結び 故に首を絞め合う患者達
Patients tying a red string tight and strangling each other,
呼吸が出来ない 然れど解けない
Unable to breathe, yet unable to untie it,
本義に反する麻酔に浸っている
Immersed in an anesthesia that defies reason.
ただ心の溝をそっと覆いたくて
Just wanting to gently cover the gap in my heart,
たったそれだけの違いなのに
Even though that should be the only difference,
どのガーゼを充てたとしても代えられない
No gauze could ever replace it.
貴方の温もりを待っている
I'm waiting for your warmth.
病名は愛だった
The disease was love.
死んじゃったらご馳走
Once we die, it's a feast,
あの世でピーッ
In the afterlife, pip!
でもそんなの楽しい？
But is that really fun?
地獄でピピピッ
Pip-pip-pip in hell!
もっと欲欲よしないデ ほら深火傷怪しげル
Don't be so greedy, look at that deep burn, suspicious!
切り替えてコンダクター
Switch it up, conductor!
注射・ベッド・手術・ムクロ・ダシ・ダシ・チュ・チュ・チュ
Injections, beds, surgery, corpses—chu-chu-chu!
ヒットでチュ・チュ・チュ でもベッドはチュ・チュ・チュ
Hits with chu-chu-chu, but beds are chu-chu-chu!
タン・タン・チュ・チュ・プラン・ダシ・ダシ・チュ・チュ・チュ
Tan-tan-chu-chu, plans, dash-dash-chu-chu-chu!
ビートに夢中・チュ・チュ 甘酸っぱい・チュ・チュ・チュ
Lost in the beat, chu-chu, bittersweet, chu-chu-chu!
もったりだの軽るだの
Heavy or light,
注射パタパヨ踊らそ踊らそ
Let's flutter our injections and dance, dance!
君達と踊れ踊れ むけんにハチハチ
Dance with you all, endlessly eight-eight,
エビバデ それでいいじゃない
Everybody, isn't that just fine?
愛されたい 誰からも愛されたいのって
Wanting to be loved, wanting to be loved by anyone,
良くないの？ 聞けないの？ ありのままの姿ならもう許してね
Is that wrong? Can't I ask? If true, please forgive me!
契約 わかったら返事
Contract, once you understand, give me an answer.
感動しました 泣けました 地獄最高
I was moved, I cried, hell is the best!
ムクロビ 死後のビッ
Corpse beauty, post-mortem beat!
足の裏まで寂しいですか？
Are you lonely down to the soles of your feet?
マリンがいるでしょ？
Marine is here for you, right?
ジュジュ・ムクロビ・シガノビ・ムクロのデッピ
Ju-ju, corpse beauty, post-mortem, corpse's depi!
待って どうせこの世なんて
Wait, after all, this world...
待って 港の一つ
Wait, just one port,
ねぇ待って 通り過ぎてくだけなのね
Hey, wait, we're just passing through, aren't we?
待って って言ったんでしょ？ だって手摺り乗り切り
Wait, didn't I say so? Because we climbed over the handrail,
旧車が通って さらったマリンの心
An old car passed by and swept away Marine's heart.
もっともなその素敵なタギったボディをくっそりごでんじゅう
Your most logical, fired-up body is taught thoroughly!
なんで整形の手術？ らしいかも見た目窓枠、頭からカラダで、おいでフェ
Why plastic surgery? It might seem like it from the window frame, head to body, come on!
なんてホントのモ・シュ・ツ・ウ・ハートビートはえ・で・ち・ゅ
What a true heartbeat is e-de-chu!
ショーは、かなりショーは、注射触れればよ・そ・ら
The show is quite a show, touch the injection yosora!
ビューティ・ビューティ・デ・ウ・ク・ス・シ・ク 笑おう、笑おう
Beauty beauty, let's smile, let's smile!
プレイ区 白紙して ギュッてして コントって終わらない
Play area, leave it blank, hug tight, the skit never ends!
目指す 好き好き 何もかも丁寧に入れてちょうだい
Aiming for love, love, put everything in carefully!
だから私なら呼吸パ いつでも死んでもなお今って
So for me, breathing pa, even if I die now, right now!
ギラ・ギラ・ギラ ノー・グラ・ダ
Glitter, glitter, glitter, no-gura-da!
近くをが近くをが 近くをが
Getting closer, getting closer, getting closer!
ギラ・ギラ・ギラ ノー・グラ・ダ ギラ・ギラ・ギラ
Glitter, glitter, glitter, no-gura-da!
月あかりを透き通りとぼりや踊れったった
Shinining through the moonlight, stumbling and dancing along,
方を立てて歌えば風が吹く
If we sing holding our shoulders, the wind blows.
月あかりをみんなまだまだ上がるんだった
Under the moonlight, everyone is still rising higher,
大波小波をかき分けてしゅっこう
Pushing through big waves and small waves, set sail!
ねぇもっともっとチュ・チュ・チュ 遊び散らかして乱ったりを
Hey, more and more, chu-chu-chu, scattering around and getting wild,
血まみれだったそこがアンダーはなんだわ良い旅を
Where it was covered in blood, underneath is a good journey,
ララララ… 踊りまわったらば
La la la... once we dance around,
踊りまわったらば むくろに花束を
Once we dance around, a bouquet for the corpse,
踊ろ踊ろしい
Eerie and dancing,
君達と踊ろ踊ろ
Let's dance and dance with you all,
無限にハッピハッピエビバデ それでもいいじゃない
Endlessly happy-happy everybody, isn't that just fine?
好き好き好き好き超愛してる
Loving, loving, loving, loving, I super love you!
do・ki・do・ki・shite rouge？
Do-ki-do-ki-shite rouge?
【いきますよ～！】
[Let's go~!]
無罪！無罪！美少女無罪！
Innocent! Innocent! Pretty Girl Innocent!
だってさ やっところんになっても
Even if I finally become an old hag,
おわらないカーニバル
the carnival never ends.
ねぇ、行ったよね？
Hey, you said it right?
年齢なんて関係ないってさ
That age doesn't matter at all,
任せて！魔法で若返り
Leave it to me, rejuvenated by magic!
秘密の素顔は君にだけ
My secret true face is just for you.
キュートは正義 美少女無罪
Cute is justice, Pretty Girl Innocent
君の一番目指してヨーソロー！
Aiming to be your number one, yosoro!
きゅきゅきゅるん きゅきゅきゅるんるん
Kyu kyu kyurun, kyu kyu kyurun run,
恋する気持ち17歳
Feeling like I'm seventeen in love!
Ahoy! 皆さん、宝鐘海賊団船長の宝鐘マリンです！
Ahoy! Everyone, Houshou Marine, Captain of the Houshou Pirates!
二日目だー！
It's the second day!
はーい！
Hooray!
いや君たち、びっくりした？あの、骸骨がさ、起き上がってびっくりしたでしょ？
Hey guys, were you startled? That the skeletons got up and surprised you?
あれ君たちだから、死んでたの
Well, that's because you guys were dead.
よかった、生き返ってくれて！おませ、君たち、宝鐘海賊団について来れるか？
I'm glad you came back to life! Can you keep up with the Houshou Pirates?
まだまだ盛り上がっていくぞ！
We're gonna keep getting more hyped!
はい、ここまでのね、あの、曲はね、結構ね、あの、なんかこう、前回、セトリに思いなんて込めてないみたいな
So up until now, these songs... Last time, I tried to act cool like I didn't put much feeling into the setlist,
なんか、事ちょっとすかしちゃいんちゃったけど、ここは込めた。
but I really put my feelings into this one.
ここ込めてます。はい、マリンのね、
I put my feelings in here. Marine's...
あの、なんですか、マリオコ、え、マリン出航、まぁ出航して、マリオコで、いやお宝だと思ったらせられて死んだみたいな感じの…
Marine set sail, set sail in Marie-go, thought she found treasure, but got locked away and died...
悲しくなんないでね、生きてます。で、そっから生き返るみたいなね、感じのストーリー仕立てになりましたー！
Don't be sad, she's alive! And then she comes back to life, turned into that kind of storyline!
はい！ところで、この衣装さ、昨日の初日した時とはどこか違うんだけど、どこでしょう？
Right! By the way, this outfit is slightly different from yesterday's first day. Where is it different, I wonder?
袖！そう、袖！袖でーす！袖でーす！袖でーす！
Sleeves! Yes, sleeves! The sleeves! The sleeves! The sleeves!
あとね、気付いた？ ここ、ここ、このステージ、船なんです！
And also, did you notice? Here, here, this stage is a ship!
昨日はね、全部を見せないようにしてたんだけどね、最後にバーンって出たと思うんだけど、それがね、
Yesterday, I tried not to show the whole thing, but I think it appeared with a bang at the end.
この船、これ今日ねレンタル船なんで、今日が終わったら解体です！
This ship is a rental ship today, so once today is over, it gets dismantled!
わあ…
Wow...
あー、君たち！君たち！嬉しいよ！
Ah, you guys! You guys! I'm so happy!
そうだ、思い出した！いくよ！
That's right, I remembered! Here we go!
分かる？マリンのギター、テクニックくれ！
Can you tell? Marine's guitar technique!
えっと、あとね、あ、いくよ！
Um, also, ah, here we go!
ちょっと待って、すいません、ちょっと音、音が、あ、音が、すいません、ちょっと待ってください、
Wait a minute, sorry, the sound... Ah, the sound, sorry, wait a minute.
マリンの、マリンの今音トラブルが起こってます。マリンの耳の、耳の方で…
Marine's... Marine is having sound trouble right now. In Marine's ear, in her ear...
ちょっと待って、待って、今、ちょっと今直してるから、こういうこともあります。
Hold on, hold on, she's fixing it right now. Things like this happen too.
あ、でも君たちの「うぉー」ってのが聞こえる、ありがとう、君たち！
Ah, but I can hear you guys going "Whoa!" Thank you, you guys!
君たち、君たちマリンの夜が破壊されても君たちの声だけは聞こえるみたい。
Even if Marine's night gets destroyed, it seems like I can still hear your voices.
あ、来た！やったー！
Ah, it's back! Yay!
いや、あきらめ、ちょっと待って、すいません、ごめん、はしゃぎすぎた、すいません。はしゃいだら切れました。
Wait, sorry, my bad. I got too excited, sorry. Once I got too excited, it cut out.
待って、あ、聞こえる！治った！君たち、やったー！やったー！
Wait, ah, I can hear it! It's fixed! You guys, yay! Yay!
いうわけでね、ちょっとすいません、色々ありましたけど、はい、ちょっとここで将棋に戻って…
Anyway, sorry about that, a lot happened, but yes, let's get back to the show here...
はい、まずは、え、今韓国の映画館でライブビューイングを実施しているんですよ！
Yes, first of all, we are currently holding a live viewing in Korean cinemas!
あんにょんはせよー！
Annyeonghaseyo!
Ahoy!!
はい。
Yes.
ここ推しカメラがね、あるんでね、推しカメラ！あるんです、ここに！
There's an oshi-camera here, you know—an oshi-camera! It's right here!
推しカメラ！
An oshi-camera!
あ、さらすよ。
Ah, I'll show it!
うん。
Yeah.
って感じで。
Something like that.
そして、配信で見てくれてる君たち！
And to all you guys watching on the stream!
あ、じゃあ推しカメラ！ 推しカメラ、君たち！配信の君たち！
Ah, then the oshi-camera! Oshi-camera, you guys! You guys on the stream!
はい中継してと。
Yes, relaying.
コメントも拾いますからね、ちゃんと今日も。はい、安心してください。
We'll be reading comments today too, so please rest assured.
ってことでね、船長との航海を最後までしてほしいんだけど、
So, you know, I want you to continue this voyage with the captain until the end...
YouTubeの無料落ち！
But YouTube's free stream cut us off!
早！判定が早い！
So fast! The cut-off is so fast!
えー、無料落ちの味さは、ここまでになっちゃう。
Uh, the free stream preview ends right here.
そうだよ、そうだよね、YouTubeの君たち！
That's right, isn't it, you guys on YouTube?
ちらみせの、無料の君たち！ チケット欲しいよね、マリンと最後まで航海したいよね！
You guys watching the free sneak peek! You want a ticket, right? You want to sail with Marine to the end!
概要欄に！あります！
It's in the description box!
なんぜひとも配信チケットを買って最後まで見てください、お願いします！
So please, by all means, buy a streaming ticket and watch until the end, I'm begging you!
はい！
Yes!
では、次の曲いきますよ！準備できてますか！？
Now then, let's go to the next song! Are you ready!?
わー！
Yay!
さあ、キミパイ！盛り上がって行くぞー！
Now, Kimi-pai! Let's get hyped up!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!